# Danny (Li-Yang) Chen

22 Ivy Bush Ave, Toronto, ON M1V 2M7
Phone: (647) 893 5474

chenliyang1024@gmail.com
Website: https://dc1024.ca/

Motivated, passionate, ambitious and detail oriented. Recent university graduate specializing in computer science and software development. With solid developing skills including **Angular2/4**, **HTML**, **SCSS** and **Android**. My previous teams developed two web applications, and eight static websites for other companies and one Android for the government. I'm looking forward to developing a software that's as groundbreaking as Apple's iPhone and iOS.

## **Skills**

#### **Technical Skills**

- Strong experience with Python, Java, JavaScript, Node.JS, Angular2/4(Typescript), Visual Basic.
- Experience with Shell Script, C, PHP, Velma, PHP, JQuery, HTML 5, CSS, SCSS.
- Familiar with MySQL, SQLite, Android Application, WIX, AWS, Heroku.
- Experienced with repository command SVN, GitHub, BitBucket.
- Cloudflare(Free SSL), Instagram Developer API, YouTube Developer API, Google Analytics, Stripe
- Strong MS Office Word, Excel and PowerPoint, Prezi skill, Agile Development
- Familiar with Linux (Ubuntu, CentOS), Mac OSX and Windows XP / 2000 / 7 / 8 / 10

#### **Interpersonal Skills**

- Strong leadership skill developed through being leader of class, student unions and teamwork projects
- Fluent and appropriate communication skill with both English and Mandarin
- Strong time management skill managing time between school work and hosting club events

# **Work Experience**

#### **Horizon Tech and Media**

- Software / Web Application developer Toronto, Canada Feb 2017 Jan 2018
- Responsible for developing web application *Canadahomestays.com* backend server with **Node.JS**, and administrator dashboard with **Angular2**, **SCSS**. (MEAN) Taking care of the cloud server from **AWS** 50%
- Responsible for developing web application *Gamie.io* prototype frontend with **VanillaJS**, and supported by **Node.JS** at the back, deployed on Heroku 90%
- Responsible for developing eight demonstrations static websites(**HTML**, **SCSS**, **JS**), and few interactions for customers on *Savvydemo.ca* 100%

#### Industrial Technology Research Institute of Taiwan, ROC

• Android Developer

- Hsinchu, Taiwan
- May 2016 August 2016
- Responsible for developing Android Application, Fubon Health App, with team. Build the **UI** part and also the **data collection from a wearable device**, and I solved a major **runtime** problem that picture (23 to 27 pictures in a second) cannot be analyzed in time. –45%
- Responsible for developing a Blockchain monitoring mobile application with team. -75%

## Staff of ROCSAUT (Republic of China Student Association at University of Toronto)

• **President** Toronto, Ontario April 2015 – April 2016

Public Relations
 Toronto, Ontario
 June 2014 – April 2015

Responsible for not only making connections between Taiwanese within campus, but also spreading out
the Taiwanese culture to everyone on campus. Organizing events, and marking connections to all
Taiwanese clubs across Eastern Canada, and other organization within Toronto.

## **Education**

**University of Toronto Scarborough** 

Toronto, Ontario

2013 - 2018

# **Work Projects**

#### Web Application (VanillaJS) - FreakingMath Web Version [Self Project]

A web application having math exam, but not published.

#### Android/iOS/Web Application - Afavor [Afavor.com]

• An Application that published on Google Play and App Store. The app helps people to post favors, and help others need online or locally. Get paid by completing the tasks.

#### Web Application (Angular2/4) - Gamie.io Prototype [Horizon Tech & Media]

• A web application which supports online multiplayers gaming including math, history questions. It's now extendable to more and more kinds of different interactions such as anonymous form.

#### Web Application (MEAN) - CanadaHomestays.com [Horizon Tech & Media]

• A web application which is a platform that helps student overseas to find a local homestay family, the application is now Toronto based, and we're expanding worldwide.

#### Savvy Media Website Demos (Integration) – savvydemo.ca [Horizon Tech & Media]

 A website integrated with eight different purposes small website. It's the demonstration for customers to see what the company is capable to build, including online marketing, small business, interior design, and dessert shop.

#### Android - Fubon Health App [Industrial Technology Research Institute of Taiwan]

• A health care application cooperates with insurance company which is able to keep track of customers' health and body status. Learned more advanced Android developing skills, and mostly the interaction with Bluetooth devices and web API server.

### Android – Ethereum portable testing application [Industrial Technology Research Institute of Taiwan]

 A testing based application for Ethereum telling the details from every transaction being sent by customer, this service is usually used in FinTech and industry for which need advanced security.

# **School Projects**

#### Python – Matplotlib Library modifications [School Project – CSCD01]

Agile Scrum way of development, debug matplotlib, fix bugs, adding new features, and send pull
request to repository to make contribution to the open source.

## Python – WebWork Integration [School Project – CSCC01]

Agile Scrum way of development, developed a web application with python as a backend server,
 VanillaJS as frontend, which integrated Webwork, an open source.

## Python - SQL system [School Project - CSCC43]

 Design a Python language SQL-like system database with command prompt to access database and return valid results

#### C Language - Poll system [School Project - CSCB09]

- Design a C language command prompt poll system, ie. Doodle like system without GUI
- Learned how to set up a server with C

#### Java - Puzzle Game [School Project - CSCB07]

- A puzzle-liked game which players can control monkey to eat bananas, and the one who gets more bananas wins
- Learned most Java language implementation skills, and get familiar with class

#### Android application - Flight Booking App [School Project - CSCB07]

- Developed an android application with 3 team members using Java. Customers can use this
   Virtual app to booked flight tickets
- Learned OOP, design pattern, used CRC Model
- Displayed team working skills by collaborating and cooperation, and also improved communication skills

# Python – Hanoi Tower game [School Project – CSCA48]

• Design a Python language command prompt game, which user can input number of towers and number of disks.